Screaming "Goodbye" and "Thank you" till my voice breaks
sayonara arigatou koe no kagiri
is far more important than giving in to sorrow
kanashimi yori motto daiji na koto
As I watch you go away, I want to let you know
sariyuku senaka ni tsutaetakute
I'll be ready to face anything, come rain or shine
nukumori to itami ni maniau you ni
I always thought what we had would last forever
kono mama tsuzuku to omotteita
Within my mind, I painted our days together
bokura no ashita wo egaiteita
Now I'm calling out to you
yobiatteita
to show you the embers
hikari ga mada
that still burn bright in my heart
mune no oku ni atsui no ni
We met amidst a blazing journey
bokutachi wa moesakaru tabi no tochuu de deai
We came together; we let go—for the sake of the future
te wo tori soshite hanashita mirai no tame ni
If any of my dreams were to come true
yume ga hitotsu kanau tabi
I'll have you to thank for it
boku wa kimi wo omou darou
Vowing to get stronger, I let my tears flow
tsuyoku naritai to negai naita
As we part ways, with this resolve inside me
ketsui wo hanamuke ni
Held captive by my memories and nostalgia
natsukashii omoi ni torawaretai
Wailing at the cruelty of this world
zankoku na sekai ni nakisakende
It will only get worse as time goes on
otona ni naru hodo fuete yuku
I don't want to lose anything—never again
mou nani hitotsu datte ushinaitakunai
If I stop trying and give in to sadness
kanashimi ni nomare ochite shimaeba
I might be able to escape this pain
itami wo kanjinaku naru keredo
But your words echoing
kimi no kotoba
all your wishes and dreams
kimi no negai
kimi no koe
I swore to protect them till the end
boku wa mamorinuku to chikattan da
With a roar, it's crumbling—crashing around me
oto wo tatete kuzure ochite yuku
Our one and only, irreplaceable world
hitotsu dake no
kakegae no nai sekai
The spark I reached my hand out to protect
te wo nobashi dakitometa hageshii hikari no taba
It burst into flames; it went out—for the sake of the future
kagayaite kietetta mirai no tame ni
Holding on to the hopes and dreams I've been entrusted with
takusareta shiawase to yakusoku wo koete yuku
I will keep pushing on without ever looking back
furikaerazu ni susumu kara
I will look straight ahead, no matter if I cry
mae dake muite sakebu kara
Setting my heart ablaze, I'll keep moving ahead
kokoro ni homura wo tomoshite
Until I reach that distant future
tooi mirai made