Kenichi.
Hideki.
Minoru.
Masao.
Susumu.
Yuta.
Yaichi.
Toyoaki.
Isao.
Ryosuke.
Yukio.
Takahiro.
Master, we should return.
It's not good for your health.
I don't know how many times I can come back here.
While I'm still in charge, I'd like to settle the scores
for all these children who lost their lives.
I've received as many as seven reports of demon catastrophes just this month.
My children in the Demon Slayers
are still on the front lines, fighting them, even as we speak.
No matter how many lives the demons snuff out,
they can never extinguish
the bright embers of a human spirit.
However battered we are,
we will always rise up to fight again.
Let's hide our swords on our backs for now.
Oh, crap! The train's leaving!
Are the cops still around?
We'll have to go even if they are.
I'm taking you head-on, master of the land!
Hang on, you idiot!
We should go, too!
Hey, don't leave me behind!
W-Wait up!
Tanjiro! Inosuke!
Zenitsu!
Man, it's fast!
Sorry! We're very sorry!
Forget that! Get over here, dumbass!
So freakin' fast!
Ma'am, is that all right?
Thank you kindly.
Sorry to trouble you.
Oh no.
It's the least I could do.
This Rengoku guy, he's a Hashira, right?
Are you sure you'll recognize him?
Yep.
He had this firey hairstyle,
and I remember his scent as well.
I think I'll know once we get close.
Delicious!
Is that the Flame Hashira?
Yeah...
Not just some random glutton?
Delicious!
Yeah...
Um, excuse me...
Delicious!
You're Rengoku, right?
Y-Yeah, we kinda heard you the first ten times.
And you're the kid from that day at the Master's.
Yes.
I'm Kamado Tanjiro.
And these are my fellow Demon Slayers, Agatsuma Zenitsu and Hashibira Inosuke.
I see.
And inside that box must be...
Yes, it's my sister, Nezuko.
Right!
That demon we saw back then, huh?
Since the Master's acknowledged her,
I won't question it.
Here, have a seat.
Incredible! I'm actually inside this titan!
You're gonna break the glass!
Cool your jets, will ya?
What brings the three of you here?
A mission, perhaps?
We received an order from the Kasugai Crow.
We were told to join you since the casualties on the Infinite Train were on the rise.
Right! I see now! Understood!
Yessir.
And there's another reason...
There's something I wanted to ask you.
What's the matter? Let's hear it.
It's about my father.
What about your father?
Well, he was a frail man.
Was he now?
And yet he could perform his
Dance of the Fire God even in freezing weather.
Glad to hear it!
The thing is...
What is it?
The Dance of the Fire God's Waltz...
I suddenly found myself doing that dance
just like my father used to.
I was hoping if you knew anything about that,
you'd be willing to tell me.
Right!
But I know nothing!
It's the first I've heard of this "Dance of the Fire God."
But it's truly commendable that
you were able to adapt his dance to battle.
All right, end of discussion!
Um, can you at least try to help a little?
You should become my Tsuguko!
I'll take good care of you!
Hold on a second!
And just what are you looking at?!
He's a weirdo, all right.
Flame Breathing has a long history.
In every era, there's always been a Flame and a Water swordsman among the Hashira.
Flame.
Water.
Wind.
Stone.
Thunder.
Those are the fundamental breathing techniques.
All other techniques are derived from those five.
Like how Mist is a branch of Wind.
Young Mizoguchi!
What color is your sword?
My name's Kamado and the sword's color is black.
A black sword, huh?
Well, isn't that unfortunate?
Unfortunate, how?
I've never heard of someone
with a black sword become a Hashira.
Not to mention, I'm told they
have no clue which style to master.
Come to me and I'll train you!
You can rest easy now!
N-No, thank you!
And what exactly are you looking at?!
He's a strange one, but he's got a good heart.
And I can smell he has a strong sense of justice.
Holy fucking shit—it's fast!
That's dangerous, you moron!
I'mma go outside and challenge it to a race!
You can't possibly be that dumb, right?
That's dangerous!
You never know when a demon might show up.
You're kidding, right?
Demons show up on this train?
Sure do!
Seriously?!
No!
So we're not going to them? They're coming for us?!
Oh god, no!
Lemme get off!
Over forty people have gone missing from this train.
The Slayers sent a few men, but they all went silent.
That's why a Hashira such as myself is here.
All right!
I'm getting off!
Lemme off!
May I...
see your...
tickets, please?
What's he doing?
The conductor's going to check your ticket and punch a hole in it.
Here.
What's that smell?
It's horrible.
Thank you...
very much.
Mr. Conductor,
you could get hurt, so please step back.
As this is an emergency,
please overlook the fact that I have a sword.
Was it your Blood Art that hid that massive body?
I had a hard time detecting you.
Remember this:
If you bare your fangs at the innocent,
my crimson blade of fire will burn you to the bone!
Flame Breathing.
First Form.
Oblivious Fire!
Amazing.
He sliced its head off with a single blow.
There is another.
Follow me!
D-Don't leave me behind!
You will not lay a finger on that man!
Didn't you hear?
Your opponent stands right before you.
What the hell is that?
Its arms are so friggin' long!
All right!
First come, first served!
Hold up!
We have to save the passengers first!
Won't matter once I obliterate this thing!
You'll be safe in the back.
Go on.
Now we're good to go.
Let's finish him off quickly.
Flame Breathing.
Second Form.
Rising Scorching Sun!
Tha—
Th-Tha—
That was awesome, Bro!
Talk about brilliant sword skills, man!
Please make me your apprentice!
Sure! I'll make a fine swordsman out of you!
Me, too, please!
Me, three!
I'll train all of you!
Big Bro Rengoku!
Bro!
I did as I was told.
I punched their tickets and put them to sleep!
Please! Do the same to me as well!
Let me be reunited with my dead wife and daughter!
I'm begging you!
I'm begging you, please!
Sure thing.
You did well.
Now, go to sleep.
Dream that you are with your family again.
Excuse me.
What would you like us to do?
Soon enough, their slumber will grow deeper.
Wait here until then.
Perceptive demon hunters sometimes wake up, sensing the presence of bloodthirsty demons.
So when you tie the ropes,
be careful not to touch their bodies.
I must remain in the first car for the time being.
Hang on until everything's ready to go.
Then, you may have blissful dreams as well.
Understood.
What's going on? What happened?
Calm down.
Just calm down.
You have to calm down.
Hey!
It's Tanjiro!
Welcome home!
Did you sell the charcoal?
What's wrong?
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
What better way to die than to die while dreaming!
Your strength as a demon hunter is of no relevance.
A human's driving force
comes from the heart—the spirit!
All you have to do is destroy their spiritual core
and they'll die, just like that!
All human hearts are the same.
Weak and fragile, like glasswork.
We have to tie ourselves to them by the wrist, right?
Correct.
Don't forget what he warned us about.
Take slow and deep breaths,
then start counting upwards.
Do that and you'll fall asleep.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
And then, we were both surprised because Tanjiro suddenly burst into tears!
What a weirdo!
Oh my, you must be exhausted.
It's not that big a deal. I'm fine.
You don't have a fever, do you?
Take it easy and get some rest today, okay?
I'm fine.
Are you sure?
Hey! Come back here!
Gotcha!
What do you think you're doing?!
C'mon! Cut it out already!
I guess...
I was having a bad dream or something.
They continue to fall, deep in their dreams.
They forget to breathe, deep in their dreams.
Even if a demon comes, deep in their dreams.
Even if they're eaten up, deep in their dreams.
Must be fun.
I wonder if they're starting to find
happiness in their dreams.
Fall deeper.
And deeper still...
into your dream.
It'll be a deep slumber.
And then,
you shall never wake up again.
C'mon! This way!
The peaches over here are delicious!
And with the white clovers in full bloom,
I can make you a ring of flowers!
I'll make some really great-looking ones
for you, Nezuko!
Sure! Make lots of them!
All right, Zenitsu?
There's a river along the way,
but don't worry, it's not too deep.
Really?
Oh dear, Zenitsu!
What should I do? I can't swim!
I-I'll carry you on my back and jump right across!
I won't even let your toes get wet!
Just leave it to me!
Let's go!
Expedition Team! Expedition Team!
We are the Cave Expedition Team!
Boss!
What's up, Underling 1 and Underling 2?
I can smell the master of this cave over there, pompoko!
And I can hear it breathing as it sleeps, squeak!
There he is!
All right, let's go!
It's on!
Roger that, Boss!
Hey, you!
Come along, Underling 3!
Over here!
Look, I'll give you these sparkly acorns! C'mon!
Bring it on!
What did I come here for?
Oh, right.
To report to my father.
To tell him that I've become a Hashira.
So what if you're a Hashira now?
It's a worthless title.
It means nothing.
You will never amount to anything.
Neither you
nor I.
Brother!
Was father pleased to hear the news?
Do you think he will acknowledge me
if I became a Hashira as well?
He wasn't always like that.
In fact, he was once a Hashira himself.
He was a passionate man.
And yet, one day, out of the blue,
he quit being a swordsman.
Just like that.
The man who had raised us both with such enthusiasm...
Why?
There's no point in dwelling on this now.
Senjuro has been through even worse.
He barely has any memories of our mother
who died of illness when he was young,
and just look at the state father is in.
I'm going to be honest.
Father wasn't happy to hear it.
He told me that it meant nothing.
But that's not enough to extinguish my passion!
The flame inside my heart will never go out!
I will never give in!
Listen closely, Senjuro.
You and I are different.
You have a big brother.
A brother who believes in you!
Whatever path you take,
you're going to become a fine man!
Just keep that burning passion inside your heart and give it your all!
Let us both keep doing our best!
No matter how lonely it gets.
Looking good.
The ropes I created allow one to invade the dreams of whoever they're tethered to.
I always exercise the utmost caution with my plans.
Once you're asleep, Hashira or not, you're no different than a baby.
I'm so going to enjoy the feast
after I've disposed of the demon hunters.
No need to tense up so much.
Relax your shoulders.
Like this?
That's right.
That was close. He's right around the corner.
I have to make sure he doesn't see me!
I need to get to the edge of the dream!
Quickly!
The world of dreams I show them isn't infinite.
It's circular, with the dreamer at its center.
Outside the dream is the realm of the subconscious,
where you'll find the spiritual core.
That is what you must destroy.
Do that, and the dreamer
will be reduced to a hollow shell.
There it is!
I can see further but I can't move beyond this point.
I'll destroy his spiritual core right away!
And then, I'll get to experience a happy dream myself!
What an odd subconscious realm.
All this fire, it's so hot.
I must hurry.
Found it!
The spiritual core!
I've never seen a red one before.
All I have to do is destroy this...
And then it'll be my turn...
I thought humans couldn't move while they were under the spell.
Such a strong survival instinct!
I'm going to make your favorite rice crackers today, Tanjiro.
I'll start breaking old rice cakes first.
It's our lucky day, Rokuta!
We're getting rice crackers!
No fair!
Tanjiro is not the only one who likes rice crackers!
I like them, too!
Me, too!
Then, let's have them together, okay?
Can you get the grill ready for me?
All right!
I'll crush them up in the grinding bowl!
Okay, I'll be in charge of flipping them over!
I'll help, too!
Well then, I'll be in charge of eating them!
No fair!
Let's go, Nezuko.
Why did I just say that?
I'm back!
Welcome home, Tanjiro.
Yeah, good to be home!
Welcome home, Tanjiro!
Wait, where's Nezuko?
Sis went up the mountain to pick vegetables.
In broad daylight?
She's not supposed to?
Well...
Um...
Tanjiro,
could you get the bath ready?
I'll have my hands full with this for a while.
I keep saying all these strange things.
Maybe I'm just tired.
Huh? It's gone.
I wonder what that was just now.
A toolbox, perhaps?
I guess my eyes are playing tricks on me.
Wake up!
You have to wake up!
You're in danger!
It's a dream!
It's all just a dream!
Wake up, now!
I see.
Right now...
I'm onboard the train!
Wake up and fight!
Fight!
Hey, Tanjiro, gimme your pickled radishes!
No, you don't! Stop it right now!
Why are you always taking food away from him?
What's your problem?
You just had seconds!
No good! I'm not awake yet!
I'm still inside the dream!
How do I get out?
Even knowing that it's a dream...
What am I supposed to do?
I have to wake up...
Big Bro!
What should we do? The fire is—
Tanjiro!
That's Nezuko's scent!
It's her blood!
Nezuko...
Nezuko!
My uniform and Sun Blade are back.
I'm waking up!
Little by little! I can feel it!
Tanjiro?
Are you okay, Big Bro?
Brother?
Sorry.
I have to go.
I have to hurry back!
I'm sorry.
Tanjiro!
Big Bro!
Brother!
If the demon who's showing me this dream is nearby...
I have to find and defeat him quickly!
Where is he?
I have to...
Where are you going, Tanjiro?
I picked lots of veggies today!
Mom! He went this way!
He just burst into flames all of a sudden!
Mom?
Are you all right, Tanjiro?
Big Bro...
What's the matter, dear?
Why are you dressed like that?
I wish I could stay here...
forever.
I wish I could just turn around and go back.
Just like how it should've been from the start.
Right here.
If things had been as they should've...
you would all be alive and well.
And Nezuko would be able to go
out in the sunlight, under the blue sky.
If it was as it should've been...
If none of that ever happened...
I'd be making charcoal here every day.
I never would've even touched a sword!
If only this wasn't a dream...
If only this was real...
But it's too late now.
I can never go back!
Big Bro!
Don't leave us behind!
Sorry!
I'm sorry, Rokuta!
We can't be together anymore.
But you'll forever be in my heart.
All of you will always be in my heart!
There are too many things I need to thank you for.
Too many things I need to apologize for!
I can't possibly forget you!
My heart will always be with you, no matter what!
So, please...
please forgive me!
I must hurry and destroy his spiritual core.
So, this is what's inside of his soul?
How can it be so beautiful?
It stretches out to the horizon...
and...
it's so warm.
Where the heck is this spiritual core thing, anyway?
And what's with this subconscious realm?
That naked boar-man was so creepy.
This is driving me insane!
What are you even doing in here?
You gross naked boar-headed freak!
It's pitch-dark.
I can't see a damn thing in here.
This sucks.
What is wrong with this
blond brat's subconscious realm?
Do I have to fumble around to find his spiritual core?
You gotta be kidding me.
What was that?
What the hell's a dude doing in here?
Damn you, parasite!
The only person allowed in here is Nezuko!
I'm so gonna kill you.
Where's Nezuko?
Wh-Who the heck knows?
All right, then...
Die!
No!
Things aren't going well, are they?
I wonder why.
They haven't destroyed any of the spiritual cores yet.
Oh well...
I guess it doesn't matter,
as long as they're buying me some time.
Not here.
But I can smell him, just barely.
Something's off, though.
It's like there's a film over everything!
The faint demonic scent is all over the place!
I can't tell the exact location!
I've gotta hurry!
I can tell that Nezuko is hurt!
If everyone else is out as well, we're in big trouble!
What should I do?
Can't I use Total Concentration Breathing?
Am I just asleep right now?
Tanjiro.
Take up your sword.
There's something you must cut down.
There's something...
I must cut down.
There's something I must cut down
in order to wake up.
I think I know what it is.
But what if I'm wrong?
If what happens in here has an effect out there,
it'll all be over!
Don't hesitate! Do it!
You have to!
My death in this dream will lead me to reality!
In other words,
what I have to cut down
is my own neck!
It's okay. I'm alive.
Nezuko! Are you okay?
I'm so glad, Nezuko.
Zenitsu.
Inosuke.
Rengoku.
Who are these people?
They're all tied to the others with ropes.
Ropes?
What is this?
It's burned off.
Nezuko's burning blood did it?
It's faint, but I'm picking up a demon's scent, too!
This smell...
It's the ticket!
I knew it. It's giving off the same scent.
We were put to sleep when our tickets were punched.
A demon must be behind this!
Did he unleash such a strong
Blood Art with just this faint scent?
I don't know why, but...
I have a feeling that I shouldn't sever this rope with my Sun Blade.
Nezuko! Do me a favor!
I want you to burn off everyone's ropes!
Zenitsu! Wake up!
Get up, Zenitsu!
You've gotta wake up!
Wake up, Inosuke! Please!
Inosuke...
Attagirl.
I'm sorry, okay?
Thanks. You did a great job, Nezuko.
It didn't work.
They're still asleep.
What should I do?
Rengoku—
What are you doing?
Is a demon controlling her?
Get out of our way!
We won't get to have our dreams
just because of you guys!
Is she acting on her own?
This guy, too?
What do you think you're doing?
If you're awake, you'd better help us out!
You may have Tuberculosis or whatever,
but if you don't help out,
I'll go tell him and he won't
show you any dreams, y'hear me?
Is he the one who was connected to me?
She said he has Tuberculosis.
How awful.
It's unforgivable,
taking advantage of their weakness!
I'm sorry.
I have no choice but to fight back.
You want to stay inside a happy dream, don't you?
I get it.
I wanted to stay inside mine, too.
If only this was the dream...
To think...
I was willing to hurt others
to escape the pain of my illness.
How cold and selfish of me.
But inside your dream, your soul was so warm.
You must be the incarnations of this boy's soul.
The sky is so clear and relaxing.
Is that his spiritual core?
Why bring me here?
Because I was searching for it?
That's why?
Even when...
I was trying to destroy it?
Why would you...
The shining little sprites within you
lit up my heart as well.
Are you all right?
Thank you.
Be careful.
Right!
Nezuko!
The scent is too strong!
It's the demon!
His scent overpowering even in this strong wind!
How did I manage to sleep through it?
Even if each car was closed off and airtight,
it's unbelievable!
I was totally useless!
The demon is upwind.
Is he in the first car?
It's dangerous, Nezuko!
Stay there and wait for me!
Go wake everyone up!
What's this? Awake already?
Morning!
You could've stayed in a bit longer!
It was him!
Why are you awake, anyway?
Did I not show you the sweetest dream?
I could've shown you a dream
where your family was being slaughtered.
Would you have liked that one better?
No, of course not.
Much too distressing, right?
All right, how about this?
Why don't I show you a dream
where your father comes back to life?
What I really love...
is showing people happy little dreams,
right before submerging
them into their worst nightmare.
I just adore the sight of a distorted human face.
I get such a kick out of it!
How enthralling is it to gaze at someone shattered by misfortune, squirming in agony!
I can't get enough of it!
However, I never let my guard down.
My methods might be roundabout, but I will kill the demon hunters for certain.
I just had to mix my blood with the ink on the tickets.
And once the conductor punched a hole in them,
creating clamp marks,
the spell was activated.
And yet...
how did this one manage to wake up?
And he figured it out in such a short time.
How could this be when the human desire
for a cheerful world of their own imagination
is of such great magnitude!
Intruding on one's soul is something I won't allow!
I won't ever let you get away with this!
What's this?
Those earrings he's wearing...
How lucky is that?
He came straight to me!
Could this be a dream?
Now I can receive an even
greater share of Master Muzan's blood!
And once I become more powerful,
I can even challenge a Waxing Six and usurp their place!
Water Breathing.
Tenth Form.
The Wheel of Life!
Blood Arts.
Whispers of Forced Unconscious: Hypnosis.
Go to sleep!
It didn't work?
Go to sleep.
Go to sleep!
It's not working, but why?
No, it's impossible!
He's falling under the spell over and over.
But he becomes aware of it right away,
and takes his own life in order to reawaken!
To commit suicide like that even if it's in a dream...
To take his own life with his own hands,
that takes incredible willpower!
This little bastard...
He's out of his mind!
Why didn't you save us?
Where the hell were you
when we were being murdered?
Why were you the only one to survive?
What do you think you were here for?
You're so useless!
You're the one who should've died.
How dare you go on living without a care.
There's no way they'd ever say that!
Not ever! Not my family!
How dare you
insult
their memory!
That was way too easy.
Is it possible that this is a dream?
Or was this demon just weaker than him?
I think I get it now.
I see why the Master ordered me
to dispose of you along with the Hashira.
I totally understand now!
Your very existence is just...
It just grates on my nerves, you know!
He's still alive?
Oh, that look on your face is so delightful!
That's the look I've been longing to see!
You're wondering why I'm not dead
even after you decapitated me, aren't you?
Fine, I'll tell you since I'm feeling so ecstatic.
It's so simple even an infant would understand.
It's because that thing
over there was not my main body.
Same rings true for what's talking to you right now.
It might look like my head but that is not the case.
While you were snoozing away,
I fused my being with this entire train!
Every inch of it has become my blood, flesh, and bone!
Look at your face.
Do you understand the implications now?
Over two hundred passengers on this train are food that will strengthen my body,
as well as my hostages!
Do you think you can protect them by yourself?
All these humans squirming the train from stem to stern,
can you alone keep me from devouring them?
What should I do? What can I do?
I can protect only two cars at most!
Any more is just too much for me to handle!
Rengoku! Zenitsu! Inosuke!
This is no time to be sleeping!
Wake up already, will you? Please!
Nezuko!
Protect the passengers who are asleep!
Follow me, damn minions!
All right!
Explosive Awakening!
Clear the way!
Lord Inosuke is comin' through!
Inosuke!
No corner of this train is safe anymore!
We have to protect everyone who's asleep!
The whole train has been taken over by a demon!
I repeat!
This whole train is a demon!
I knew it!
I was right on the money!
That means I was a total stud as the boss!
Beast Breathing!
Fifth Fang!
Rip and Shred!
I'll save every last one of y'all!
Then I'll have you fall to your knees!
And worship me!
As your savior!
Lord Hashibira Inosuke is comin' through!
I have to save the others!
If Inosuke can hold down the fort here,
I should go on ahead!
The situation is this bad already?
Water Breathing.
First Form.
Water Surface Slash!
Not enough.
There's no end to this!
How am I supposed to fend it off?
I can feel them scurrying around inside me.
Thrash around all you want,
but I'll just keep regenerating.
And then, after all your strength is depleted
I'll take my oh-so-sweet time
feasting on those two hundred passengers.
Thunder Breathing.
First Form.
Thunderclap and Flash!
Sixfold.
I'll protect you, Nezuko!
Protecc...
That sounded like thunder.
From one of the cars in the back?
What's going on?
Is Zenitsu awake?
What about Rengoku?
And Nezuko?
It's all I can do to protect the ones here!
This is bad! What should I do?
We can't fight in coordination!
Are the passengers in the back all right?
Damn it!
It's too cramped!
I can't swing my sword!
To think all this happened while I was napping.
How preposterous!
Some Hashira I am!
If only I could
crawl under a rock!
What the—
What was that?
A demon attack?
Young Kamado!
Rengoku!
I was quite thorough with
my bladework on my way here,
so it should take the demon a while to regenerate.
But there's no time to lose! I'll keep it short!
Right!
This train has eight cars in all.
I'll protect the five in the rear.
The Boy of Yellow and the Kamado Sister
will defend the remaining three.
During all of this,
you and the Boar Head Boy
will search for the demon's head.
Head?
But this demon is—
No matter what form it assumes,
so long as it's a demon, it's got a head!
I'll search for it while fighting, as well!
Show me how fired up you are!
Amazing! It's like he just disappeared!
Did the train shake earlier because he was on the move?
His tactical mind is just as quick, too!
Five cars, all by himself?
This is no time to be dazzled, you idiot!
Do what you have to do!
The demon's scent is getting stronger by the second!
I have to hurry!
Inosuke! Where are you, Inosuke?
Shut up or I'll end ya!
Up there, huh?
How dare that Goggle-eyes order me around!
But he was kinda...
Sorta...
He was pretty fuckin' cool!
And it pisses me off!
Inosuke! Keep an eye on the first three cars!
You ain't gotta tell me that!
And by the way, I've found it!
Already!
Thanks to my all-out Seventh Form,
I found the master's weak spot!
You did?
So, it is up front!
That's right, straight ahead!
And that front part is a heck of a lot creepier!
I can't pick up the scent because of the wind,
but if Inosuke says so, there's no doubt about it!
Is it around where the coal's loaded?
Exactly!
Got it!
All right, let's go!
Forward!
This is it, huh?
Hell yeah!
Inosuke!
Something's fishy, very fishy!
Especially around here!
Who the hell are you?
G-Get outta here!
It's here, the demon's head.
The demon's
weakness!
Gross!
Get away from me!
Just how many hands—
Shit!
Water Breathing.
Sixth Form.
Maelström!
Are you all right, Inosuke?
Don't act like you came to rescue me, okay?
Yeah, I know!
It's here.
Right under us!
The demon's scent is strongest directly below this place.
Inosuke! The demon's head is under here!
Don't order me around! I'm the boss!
Fine!
Just watch.
Beast Breathing.
Second Fang.
Hack and Slash!
This is...
It's his neck bone!
Water Breathing.
Eighth Form.
Waterfall Basin!
It blocked!
The gash is closing up!
It's regenerating so fast!
Not to mention, it took everything I had just to expose the bone!
I have to sever it!
Inosuke! Let's synchronize our breathing and attack together!
One of us will slash the flesh while the other jumps in to sever the bone!
Y'know what?
That's a great idea!
Good thinkin'!
Thanks!
Let's do this!
Eyes of Forced Unconscious: Sleep.
A Blood Art!
He got me! I'm falling asleep!
Inosuke!
Slash your own neck inside your dream!
It'll wake you up!
It's all right!
I can still break the spell!
Keep your eyes closed, idiot!
You'll just fall asleep again otherwise!
All right, I'm awake!
The moment I wake up, I can't help but look directly into one of those demon eyes!
I've gotta keep them closed when I wake up!
I have to keep my eyes shut!
Again!
Wake up!
You have to wake up!
Hurry!
Sever the neck!
Cut it!
Slash it!
It's just a dream!
There's no time left!
I have to wake up!
This isn't a dream, dumbass!
Don't fall for the trap!
Don't die such pathetic deaths!
I'm wearing the hide of the mountain god on my head.
I bet he's too scared to look me in the eye!
You loser eyeballs!
I see.
He's having a hard time
telling which way Inosuke is looking!
All right!
Now we just gotta rip this thing to shreds!
Inosuke!
Don't you dare get in the way of my dream!
Did he just stab you?
I'm okay.
Just forget about that bastard!
I can't do that! I won't let him die!
If we don't chop this thing's head off soon,
none of us will make it!
I hear you! Let's get moving!
Inosuke!
Let's synchronize our breathing!
We'll attack together and chop off the demon's head!
Not good!
If I fall asleep now...
I got ya!
C'mon! Follow my lead!
Beast Breathing.
Fourth Fang.
Slice and Dice!
Father, please guide my blade!
I'm going to sever that bone
with this strike!
Dance of the Fire God!
Azure Heaven!
Those are some death throes!
The train's turning over!
Inosuke—
Hey! Is your gut all right?!
Y-Yeah!
Inosuke, protect the passen—
I can't die.
If I die, that'll make him a murderer!
I have to survive!
I won't let anyone die!
Are you okay, Santaro?
Pull yourself together!
I was lucky I could jump off the demon's flesh!
Shoulda seen me bounce!
Your gut feeling any better?
You got stabbed, dammit!
I'm all right.
What about you?
Never been better!
Not a scratch on me!
I won't be able to move for a while.
Can you go help the others?
Was anyone injured?
What about the engineer up front?
Let the bastard die for all I care!
We can't...
He's the one who stabbed you, remember?
His leg got crushed.
He can't even move anymore!
There's no way he can walk like that!
Just let him rot!
Then he's suffered enough already.
Help him out, will you?
Please.
I'll do it for you, then!
Because I'm a good boss!
Only because my minion asked me to!
But after I'm done rescuing, I'll rip all his hair out!
Please don't.
It's almost dawn.
Get your breathing under control.
We have to...
save the injured...
before it's too late.
Nezuko.
Zenitsu.
Rengoku.
I'm sure they're all safe!
You have to believe in them!
My body is disintegrating. I can't regenerate.
Did I lose? Am I going to die?
Me?
Ridiculous.
Absurd!
There was so much more to do!
I couldn't devour a single human!
My plan to fuse with the train
and eat everyone just went up in smoke!
And look what I've been reduced to!
After all the time and effort I put in!
All because of him!
It's all his fault!
I had taken hundreds of hostages,
but he still cornered me and pinned me down!
Is this the power of a Hashira?
And that brat...
He was so fast.
He never even broke out of my spell!
Not to mention, that girl!
She's a demon!
What's up with that?
A demon joining forces with demon hunters?
Why hasn't Master Muzan executed this traitor?
Damn it!
Damn it all!
It all started going to hell when he broke out of my spell!
He's to blame for this!
If nothing else, I want to kill that bastard!
No matter what!
And that boar head, as well!
I could've killed this bastard if it wasn't for him!
That boar thwarted me.
His intuition was extraordinary!
He could sense my gaze!
Have I truly lost?
Is this the end?
Oh, what a despicable nightmare this is!
What an awful, horrible nightmare!
It's always us Waning Moons
who get killed by the demon hunters.
The members of the Waxing Six have remained unchanged for over a century.
They're strong enough to defeat Hashira
who have killed an untold number of demons.
Do they have otherworldly powers?
Even after receiving so much of his blood,
I couldn't compete with them!
I want to do it over!
I want one more chance!
What a terrible, wretched nightmare this is!
I see you've mastered
Perpetual Concentration Breathing.
Very impressive!
Rengoku...
It is the first step toward becoming a Hashira, after all.
But that's just the first of the thousands yet to come!
I'll do my best.
You're bleeding from the gut.
Concentrate harder and take control of your breathing.
Picture your nerves reaching every part of your body.
Can you see the blood vessels?
The one which is torn.
Concentrate harder!
That's it.
Stanch it.
Stop the bleeding.
Focus!
Great! Looks like you succeeded.
There are lots of things you can do if you master breathing.
Not that you'll be able to do everything,
but you'll be much stronger than you were the day before.
Right.
Everyone else is safe!
Lots of injuries, but no one's life is in danger.
So don't strain yourself.
Take it easy and rest up.
Thank you.
Those eyes! He's the Waxing Three!
Why has he come here?
Flame Breathing.
Second Form.
Rising Scorching Sun!
That's a fine blade.
His speed of regeneration,
and this heavy, overwhelming aura...
So, this is a Waxing Moon.
Now why would someone
as powerful as you attack the wounded?
I thought he might interrupt the
little chit-chat that we're about to have.
What exactly are we going to talk about?
This might be our first meeting, but I already hate you.
Is that right?
Well, I loathe weak humans too.
The mere sight of them makes my skin crawl.
Then it seems the two of us will never see eye to eye.
Hear me out, I have a brilliant proposal for you.
Why don't you become a demon as well?
No, thanks.
Just from a glance, I can tell you're strong.
You're a Hashira, aren't you?
Your fighting spirit has been honed to the hilt.
It's close to the edge of perfection.
I'm the Flame Hashira, Rengoku Kyojuro.
I'm Akaza.
Kyojuro,
let me tell you why you'll never truly reach perfection.
It's because you're just a human.
Destined to grow old and eventually die.
Become a demon, Kyojuro.
If you do, you can go on training for hundreds of years and keep getting stronger.
Of all the demons I've come across, this one smells the most like Kibutsuji!
I have to help fight him!
Both growing old and passing away
are things that make being human beautiful.
It's precisely because of those that our lives
are all the more precious and honorable.
Strength isn't a word that
means much in regards to the flesh.
This boy is not weak!
Don't insult him.
I'll repeat it as many times as it takes.
The two of us will never see eye to eye.
No matter what the reason,
I will not become a demon!
I see.
Technique Development.
Destructive Death! Compass Needle!
I guess I'll just have to kill you then.
I can't even follow their movements!
There were never any Flames
among all the Hashira I've killed so far.
None of them ever took me up on my offer, either.
I wonder why!
As a fellow warrior,
I just can't wrap my head around it.
Not when only the chosen few get the chance!
Watching the hideous decline of
someone blessed with extraordinary powers...
It pains me! I can't bear it!
Die for me, Kyojuro.
Die while you're young and strong.
Destructive Death.
Air Type!
I see.
Flame Breathing.
Fourth Form.
Fire Whirl!
He strikes the empty air,
but the impact comes directly at me!
The strikes travel instantly.
If I keep fighting from a distance,
it'll be tough to slice his head off.
In that case,
I'll just have to get up close!
These extraordinary reflexes
and these breathtaking sword skills, as well.
Time will steal it all, Kyojuro!
Infuriating, isn't it?!
That's just how it goes!
That's what it means to be human!
Don't move!
If that wound reopens, it'll be fatal!
Stand back! That's an order!
Don't bother with those weaklings, Kyojuro!
Give me your best shot!
Eyes on me.
Nice moves!
Rengoku!
Ol' Goggle-eyes!
Just turn into a demon, Kyojuro.
Then, we can fight endlessly and get stronger together!
You've got what it takes!
Never!
Let me make this clear.
I do not like you!
I will not become a demon!
Flame Breathing.
Third Form.
Inferno Vault!
What a magnificent attack!
Destructive Death.
Air Type!
I want to join the fight, but there's no opening.
I just can't keep up with their speed!
Those two are on a whole other level!
Getting between them would only mean death! I can feel it in my bones!
Even if I did find an opening, I'd only be in the way!
Rengoku...
You still don't get it?!
You're only hastening your death with these attacks!
Kyojuro!
Flame Breathing, First Form.
Oblivious Fire!
It's such a shame I have to kill you now!
You haven't reached your peak yet!
Second Form.
Rising Scorching Sun!
In a few short years, your abilities
will be sharpened to an even finer point!
Third Form.
Inferno Vault!
Fourth Form.
Fire Whirl!
Destructive Death.
Fifth Form.
Blazing Tiger!
Disorder!
Kyojuro!
Did he do it? Did he win?
Don't tell me...
No way!
Let's fight some more.
Don't die on me, Kyojuro.
Rengoku...
Rengoku!
You put your life on the line,
and yet it was all for nothing, Kyojuro.
Those impressive slashes you inflicted upon me have healed already.
But what about you?
A smashed left eye, shattered ribs, and damaged internal organs.
All irreparable.
If you were a demon you'd heal in a blink of an eye.
And those would be but mere scratches.
You can struggle all you want,
but a human can never surpass a demon.
I have to go help him!
But I don't have the strength to move.
All because of this injury,
and the backlash from
using the Dance of the Fire God!
Why, Kyojuro?
Because...
I will see my duty fulfilled!
No one shall die here!
Not on my watch!
I'll inflict as much damage as quickly as possible!
Flame Breathing.
Esoteric Art!
Such tremendous fighting spirit!
Despite all those injuries,
you're full of spirit and determination!
And that ironclad stance!
You have to become a demon, Kyojuro!
Let's fight each other for all eternity!
Set your heart ablaze.
Go beyond your limits!
I am the Flame Hashira,
Rengoku Kyojuro!
Ninth Form.
rengoku
Hell Fire!
Destructive Death.
Annihilation Type!
Rengoku!
I can see—
Ren...
goku...
You'll die!
You know this wound will kill you!
Become a demon!
Say that you'll become a demon!
You're strong.
You're one of the chosen few!
Kyojuro.
Yes, Mother?
I want you to think well
about what I'm going to ask you.
Do you know why you were
born stronger than so many others?
I don't know!
It is so you can protect the weak.
Those blessed with more natural talent than others
must use their strength
for the good of the world—for the people.
It's unforgivable to use strength granted by
the heavens to hurt others or empower yourself.
Helping the weak is the duty of those born strong.
You must take this responsibility seriously and fulfill your duty.
Make sure you never forget that.
I won't!
I don't have much time left.
Having a child as strong and gentle as you was truly a blessing.
I'm counting on you.
Mother,
the honor is mine to have been born to you!
He stopped it?!
His strength is unbelievable!
Even after I've skewered his guts with my arm!
Damn it!
It's almost dawn!
I have to kill him and get out of here!
I can't pull my arm out!
I won't let you escape!
No matter what Rengoku says,
I have to do this! Right now!
I have to slice off the demon's head!
Quickly!
The sun is rising!
Its light will fall here!
I have to get away!
I've got to get away!
No way I'm ever letting go!
Not until I slice your head off!
Out of my way!
Move, Inosuke!
We have to fight! For Rengoku!
Beast Breathing.
First Fang!
Pierce and Bore!
I've got to get away from the sunlight!
That took way too long!
I need to get far away from the sun!
Don't run away!
Come back here, coward!
Turn and face me!
What the hell is that brat on about?
Does he not have a brain in his head?
I'm not running away from you guys!
I'm running away from the sun!
Besides, the battle's already been decided!
He'll run out of strength and die before long!
The Demon Slayers are always fighting you demons in the dead of the night!
Where you have the advantage!
Us humans, made of flesh and blood!
We don't regenerate as fast!
And if we lose a limb, it's gone forever!
Don't you dare run away, you bastard!
You're a coward!
You hear me, dumbass!
Rengoku is stronger than you'll ever hope to be!
He's amazing!
Rengoku didn't lose!
He didn't let anyone die!
He protected everyone!
He saw the fight through to the end!
You're the one who lost!
And victory
belongs to Rengoku!
Stop yelling already.
You'll reopen that wound.
You're badly injured, remember?
If you die, Young Kamado,
I won't have my victory anymore.
Rengoku...
Come here, lad.
Let us speak one last time.
There's something I recalled...
while I was dreaming of the past.
The Rengoku residence,
you should pay it a visit.
There are notes left by the previous Flame Hashira.
My father used to read them often,
but since I never did,
I don't know what's in them.
Within those notes,
you might find something...
about that dance you mentioned.
R-Rengoku, please don't talk any more.
Just stop the bleeding
with a breathing technique!
Isn't there a way to close up your wounds?
None.
I'll be dead soon.
I need you to hear me out while I can still talk.
Tell my little brother Senjuro
to always follow his heart,
and walk down the path he feels is right.
Tell my father
that I want him to take care of himself better.
One last thing.
Young Kamado,
I believe in your sister.
I accept her as part of our ranks.
Your sister shed blood to protect the people inside that train.
Anyone who risks their lives fighting demons to protect humans
is a rightful member of the Slayers, no matter what anyone says.
Stand tall and be proud!
If you ever feel disheartened
that you're somehow not enough,
set your heart ablaze!
Grit your teeth and look straight ahead.
If you curl up and hide, time will pass you by.
It won't comfort you or wait for you to grieve.
Don't feel bad that I'm going to die here.
As a Hashira, it's my duty to protect my juniors.
Any Hashira would've done the same.
The young buds must be allowed to bloom.
Young Kamado.
Boar Head Boy.
Boy of Yellow.
Keep learning and keep growing.
And someday,
become the next Hashira
supporting the Demon Slayers.
I believe in you.
I believe in all of you.
Mother.
Did I do well?
Did I use my blessings wisely?
Was I able to carry out my duties,
and fulfill my responsibilities?
You did perfectly fine.
When the train went off the rails,
Rengoku had unleashed all these techniques.
That must be why we managed to
avoid suffering any casualties.
It must be.
I can't believe he's gone.
Was it really a Waxing Moon?
Yeah.
Why would it come here?
Something that strong? I mean...
Yeah...
This is all so frustrating!
Just when I managed to break through one wall,
I find another, taller one, right in front of me.
All these amazing people are fighting with such skill and power just beyond it.
And I can't make it over to join them!
If I'm still stumbling around in a place like this...
How can I ever...
Can I ever become anything like Rengoku?
Quit whining already!
There's no point in sitting around, wondering about maybes!
He already said he believed in us,
so don't worry about anything other than living up to that!
All living things go back to the earth when they die!
Sobbing or sniveling won't bring them back!
Don't cry even if you're down!
No matter how pathetic or humiliated you feel,
you have to keep moving forward!
But you're crying, too.
I can see the tears flooding out from that headpiece.
I'm not crying!
Get over here! We're gonna train!
Is that so...
Rengoku has...
So, even Rengoku couldn't beat a Waxing Moon?
I don't believe it.
Praise to Amida Buddha.
Those repulsive demons,
I'll exterminate them all!
I see.
Not one of the two hundred passengers lost their lives?
Kyojuro did a splendid job, indeed.
What an incredible young man.
I'm not forlorn.
My life will soon reach its end, as well.
Soon, I'll be joining Kyojuro and the others
in the land of the dead.
Rengoku...
Rengoku.
Rengoku!